#### Contact

peterpgeyser@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/pgeyser (LinkedIn)

## Top Skills

Human Resources (HR)
Communication
Technical Support

### Certifications

IT Security: Defense against the digital dark arts

System Administration and IT Infrastructure Services

**Technical Support Fundamentals** 

Google IT Support Professional Certificate Specialization

The Bits and Bytes of Computer Networking

# Peter Geyser

Assistant Operations Manager at MSAI Consulting

Greater San Diego Area

## Summary

Bachelor's of Science in Psychology and Bachelor's of Art in Cinema Studies. Previous Camp Kesem UW volunteer coordinator and camp counselor. Previous research assistant. Previous Samsung/Google/ Asurion certified mobile device repair technician. Current Assistant Operations Manager at MSAI Consulting.

# Experience

MSAI Consulting
Assistant Operations Manager
January 2019 - Present
San Diego, CA

- -Create, implement, and evaluate all human resource department policies, procedures, and structures
- -Manage health insurance programs
- -Facilitate quarterly and annual employee performance reviews
- -Ensure all employee records are maintained and updated with new hire information or changes in employment status
- -Identify the company's hiring needs and manage the recruitment process to ensure it runs smoothly
- -Respond to employees' queries and resolve issue in a timely and professional manner
- -Manage the organization's employee database and prepare reports
- -Process payroll and manage employee time tracking
- -Assist with the implementation of new processes and procedures
- -Order supplies and maintain inventory levels
- -Interact with IT Company as a vendor manager in order to facilitate repairs, upgrades, and purchases of network and server equipment
- -Continued to also carry out duties previously held as Administrative and Technical Support Specialist

## MSAI Consulting

Administrative and Technical Support Specialist September 2018 - December 2018 (4 months)

Page 1 of 4

#### San Diego, CA

- -Providing technical assistance for questions and problems
- -Resolving problems with networks and other computer systems
- -Diagnosing system errors and other issues
- -Training other staff members on troubleshooting and diagnosing problems
- -Provide general administrative and clerical support including mailing, scanning, faxing and copying to management
- -Maintain electronic and hard copy filing system
- -Perform data entry and scan documents
- -Prepare and modify documents including correspondence, reports, drafts, memos and emails

#### uBreakiFix

3 years

Assistant Manager

August 2017 - August 2018 (1 year 1 month)

Seattle, WA

- Ensure that Store meets or exceeds sales/profit goals
- Maintains store staff by assisting in recruiting, selecting, orienting, and training employees
- Maintains operations by coordinating and enforcing operational, and personnel policies/procedures.
- Identifies current and future customer requirements by establishing rapport with potential and actual customers
- Welcome customers in professional and pleasant manner
- Ensures availability of merchandise and services by maintaining and ordering inventory
- Diagnose/troubleshoot device
- Provide recommendations for problem resolution
- Provide estimates to customer for repair, replacement according to problem diagnosis and repair/replacement recommendation
- Contributes to team effort by accomplishing related results as needed
- Protects employees and customers by providing a safe and clean store environment
- Ensure repairs meet uBreakiFix quality standards

Repair Technician September 2015 - August 2017 (2 years)

Seattle, WA

- Diagnose, troubleshoot and repair devices
- Provide recommendations for problem resolution
- Explain complex technical issues to customers in a non-technical, simple to understand manner
- Provide repair and replacement estimates to customers
- Ensure that all repairs meet or exceed uBreakiFix quality standards
- Greet customers in a friendly manner and maintain a positive work environment
- Answer phone calls to the store with a professional, courteous and friendly demeanor
- Ensure that customers have an enjoyable experience by providing superior customer service and exceeding customer expectations
- Keep track of all devices and inventory while safeguarding all store stock
- Utilize the point of sale system to maintain an accurate record of customer information and a real-time status of each repair
- Maintain the cleanliness and professional appearance of the store

University of Washington
Undergraduate Research Assistant
March 2015 - June 2016 (1 year 4 months)
Seattle, WA

Living Filipino-American Project

- -Responsible for participant management: entering participants into study, writing checks for survey payments to participants, tracking participant progress, and calling participants who have not finished survey or cashed compensatory checks
- -Assist Principal Investigator with online survey programming, editing material for the UW Institutional Review Board, and project outreach
- -Worked exclusively with the Microsoft Office Suite for day-to-day operations

## Education

University of Washington
Bachelor of Science - BS, Psychology · (2012 - 2016)

University of Washington
Bachelor of Arts - BA, Film/Cinema/Media Studies · (2012 - 2016)

University of Washington